freeresultalert.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy : FreeResultAlert.com

#### Privacy Policy for FreeResultAlert.com:

The privacy of our visitors to FreeResultAlert.com is important to us.

FreeResultAlert.com respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protecting it in all respects. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by FreeResultAlert.com and how it is used.

#### Disclaimer:

FreeResultAlert.com provided all contents links are information sources and the content to be used only for informational purpose and not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites and do not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of the content on external link and websites. The content is not copied from any other websites. However, by mistakenly any content is published on this website. We will be removed any others copyrighted content if have posted in website  
www.FreeResultAlert.com Internet site may contain links to other Internet sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

#### Content Copyright Policy:

FreeResultAlert.com provide the latest result and Answer key notifications details in India. Find here government jobs results, army results, air force results, IBPS PO Results, UPSC Results, SSC JE Results, CGL Results, CHSL Results, MTS Results, Railway Results, RRB Results, RRC Results, BSF Results, CISF Results, CRPF Results, ITBP Results, NDA Results, CDS Results, RPSC Results. We don’t provide any pornographic or illegal content. Also, we have a strict policy for the content copier or copy cats. If we find any site who copied our site content then we file a complaint about that site to google. Copying of any content of this website is strictly prohibited. If you want the article/post on our site, just use 1 or 2 lines using credit link to FreeResultAlert.com. If you find any copyright issues with or you wish to print our full articles please contact us at .The copying content of other sites is illegal if you want to be put our matter on your site(like-pictures)  then contact us.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie:

Currently, we do not use Google Adsense when we join us then all the ads cookie rules are applied.

->Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FreeResultAlert.com

->Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to https://freeresultalert.com/ and other sites on the Internet.

->Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

If users disable cookies in their browser:  
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not working properly.

#### Log Files:

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site and your Device information.

#### CAN SPAM Act:

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
We collect your email address in order to:  
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at  
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

#### Fair Information Practices:

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include having played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
• Within 7 business days  
We will notify the users via in-site notification  
• Within 7 business days  
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### Third Party Advertising:

When we use Google Adsense, Infolinks, and other third-party advertising companies to servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on FreeResultAlert.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons:

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

#### If we Changes in Privacy Policy:

FreeResultAlert.com will occasionally update this privacy policy. For material changes to this statement, However, the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be. when FreeResultAlert.com changes the policy will notify all users by placing a notice on the site.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to ASN at **admin@freeresultalert.com**
